Muhannad Salkini

Software Developer

Education

• Turkey, Karabuk University
Bachelor of Computer Engineering · (2019 - Present)

Experience

Internship, 07/2023 - 09/2023 · (2 months)
 Karabuk University – Karabuk, Turkey

Interned at Directorate of Information Technology, handling network, technical support, camera operations, and support services.

This experience enhanced my problem-solving skills and provided hands-on exposure to IT operations in an educational institution.

E-commerce, 10/2018 - 05/2022 · (3 years 7 months)
 Self-employed – Turkey

Over a period of three years and seven months, I successfully managed my own e-commerce venture in Turkey, specializing in selling 3D printers and related components.

This entrepreneurial endeavor allowed me to develop my business acumen, customer relationship management skills, and an understanding of the e-commerce landscape.

Course & Certifications

- Oracle Database Design & Programming Certificates
- Almdrasa Git and GitHub Certificate
- Stanford Uni. Supervised ML Regression and Classification
- TÜBİTAK Science Fair Participation Certificates
- AFAD Disaster Awareness Education Programs

Languages

- Arabic Native
- Turkish Native
- English Professional

Contact

mohanad.salkini@gmail.com +90 (536) 240 62 03

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/muhannad-salkini

GitHup:

github.com/muhannadsalkini

Website:

muhannad.salkini.me

Summary

I'm Muhannad, a Computer Engineering student deeply passionate about software development. I've honed my skills in website development with MERN stack, Laravel, and advanced database designs. I've also crafted APIs in C# and built different systems using ASP.net showcasing my adaptability and project management abilities.

Currently, I'm working on the MERN stack, using React and Tailwind CSS for frontend development and NodeJS and MongoDB for backend projects.

I bring leadership experience from contributing to managing several clubs like Google Developer Student Clubs (GDSC) and a commitment to excellence.

Relevant Skills

Programming Languages and Frameworks:

- PHP Frameworks: Laravel
- JavaScript Frameworks: ReactJS, Node.js (including experience with Express.js)
- C# Frameworks: .NET

Web Development:

- REST API Development
- Frontend Development: HTML5, CSS (Tailwind)
- Backend Development: JavaScript, PHP
- Database Management: MySQL, MS SQL, MongoDB
- Version Control: Git/GitHub
- Operating Systems: Windows and Linux

Personal Skills

Teamwork Self-Learning
Time Management Research
Creativity Planning

Discipline Problem Solving